Welcome to my solution for this exercise.
这是答案视频
So, for here, I had you calculate the output of our network using matrix multiplication.
在这道练习中 我要求你使用矩阵乘法计算网络的输出
So remember, we wanted to use matrix multiplication because it's more
之所以要使用矩阵乘法
efficient than doing these two separate operations of the multiplication and the sum.
是因为与单独相乘和求和相比 矩阵乘法更高效
But to do the matrix multiplication,
但是要进行矩阵乘法运算
we actually needed to change the size of our weights tensor.
我们需要更改 weights 张量的大小
So, to do that, just do weights.view 5, 1,
所以 我们输入 weights.view(5, 1)
and so this will change the shape of our weights tensor to be five rows and one column.
它会将 weights 张量的形状变成 5 行 1 列
If you remember, our features has the shape of one row and five columns,
features 的形状是 1 行 5 列
so we can do this matrix multiplication.
现在可以进行矩阵乘法运算了
So, there's just one operation that does the multiplication and the sum and just one go,
乘法和加法运算 变做一步完成
and then we again add our bias term,
然后与偏差项相加
pass it through the activation,
传入激活函数中
and we get our output.
获得输出
So, as I mentioned before, you could actually stack up
就像我之前提到的
these simple neural networks into a multi-layer neural network,
你可以将这些简单神经网络堆叠成一个多层神经网络
and this basically gives
使网络能够发现数据中的规律和联系
your network greater power to capture patterns and correlations in your data.
变得更强大
Now, instead of a simple vector for our weights,
现在 weights 不再是一个简单的向量
we actually need to use a matrix.
而是一个矩阵
So, in this case, we have our input vector and our input data x_1, x_2, x_3.
这些是输入向量 x_1 x_2 x_3
You think of this as a vector of just x, which our features.
看做 x 向量 它们是特征
Then we have weights that connect our input to one hidden unit in this middle layers,
然后是将输入与中间层级中的一个隐藏单元相连的权重
usually called the hidden layer, hidden units,
这个中间层级通常称为隐藏层 隐藏层有隐藏单元
and we have two units in this hidden layer.
这个隐藏层有 2 个单元
So then, if we have our features,
特征（输入）
our inputs as a row vector,
是行向量
if we multiply it by this first column,
与这里的第一列相乘
then we're going to get the output,
获得输出
we're going to get this value of h_1.
即 h_1 的值
Then if we take our features and multiply it by the second column,
然后使 features 与第二列相乘
then we're going to get the value for h_2.
获得 h_2 的值
So again, mathematically looking at this with matrices and vectors and linear algebra,
从数学角度来说 将这些看做矩阵和向量并进行线性代数运算
we see that to get the values for this hidden layer that
要获得这个隐藏层的值
we do a matrix multiplication between our feature vector,
我们在特征向量（x_1 到 x_n）
this x_1 to x_n,
和权重矩阵之间
and our weight matrix.
进行矩阵乘法
Then as before with these values,
然后和之前一样
we're going to pass them through
将这些值传入激活函数里
some activation function or maybe not an activation function,
或者不传入激活函数里
maybe we just want the row output of our network.
直接获取网络的原始输出
So here, I'm generating some random data, some features,
我在这里生成了一些数据
and some random weight matrices and bias terms that you'll
即一些特征 随机权重矩阵和偏差项
be using to calculate the output of a multi-layer network.
你将使用这些数据计算多层网络的输出
So, what I've built is basically we have three input features,
这个网络有 3 个输入特征
two hidden units and one output unit.
两个隐藏单元和一个输出单元
So, you can see that I've listed it here.
我在这里列出来了
So, our features we're going to create three features and this features vector here,
我们将创建三个特征 即这个 features 向量
and then we have an input equals three,
使 n_input = 3
so the shape is this, and two hidden units, one output unit.
形状是这样的 有两个隐藏单元和一个输出单元
So, these weight matrices are created using these values. All right.
使用这些值创建权重矩阵现在由你来计算
I'll leave it up to you to calculate the output for this multi-layer network.
这个多层网络的输出
Again, feel free to use the activation function defined
你可以使用之前为网络输出和隐藏层
earlier for the output of your network and the hidden layer. Cheers.
定义的激活函数加油！